[ 
  {
    "id": "00000001",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "What does HTML stands for?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["Hypertext Machine language", "Humans Talking Machine Languages", "Hypertext Multiple Language", "Hypertext Markup Language"],
      "answer": "Hypertext Markup Language"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000002",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following initializes the document type in HTML5?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["</DOCTYPE HTML>", "</DOCTYPE>", "<!DOCTYPE HTML>", "</DOCTYPE html>"],
      "answer": "<!DOCTYPE HTML>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000003",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following HTML tags is used to make text bold?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<p>", "<i>", "<li>", "<b>"],
      "answer": "<b>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000004",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following HTML tags is used to make text italic?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<p>", "<i>", "<li>", "<b>"],
      "answer": "<i>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000005",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following HTML tags is used to make an unordered list?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<ui>", "<i>", "<em>", "<ul>"],
      "answer": "<ul>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000006",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following HTML tags is used to make an ordered list?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<ul>", "<ol>", "<orderedlist>", "<olist>"],
      "answer": "<ol>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000007",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following characters is used in a closing HTML tag?",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": [".", "/", "\\", "!"],
      "answer": "/"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000008",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "What is the font-size of the <h1> heading tag?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["3.5 em", "2.17 em", "2 em", "1.5 em"],
      "answer": "2 em"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000009",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "How many heading tags are there in HTML5?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["2", "3", "5", "6"],
      "answer": "6"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000010",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "horizontal_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following attributes is used to add link to any element?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["link", "ref", "href", "newref"],
      "answer": "href"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000011",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "left_boot",
    "question": "What is the purpose of a <div></div> in HTML?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["To create different styles", "To create different sections", "To separate headings only", "To add titles"],
      "answer": "To create different sections"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000012",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following tags is used to add a line-break in HTML?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<br>", "<break>", "</break>", "</br>"],
      "answer": "</br>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000013",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "horizontal_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following attributes is used to open an hyperlink in new tab?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["tab", "href", "target", "ref"],
      "answer": "target"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000014",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "left_boot",
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct way to add a background color to the <body> in HTML?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<body color = “green”>", "<body bg-color = “green”>", "<body style = “background-color=green”>", "<body style='background-color: green;'>"],
      "answer": "<body style='background-color: green;'>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000015",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "left_boot",
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct HTML syntax to make a checkbox?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<checkbox>", "<input type='checkbox'>", "<check>", "<input type='check'>"],
      "answer": "<input type='checkbox'>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000017",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "short_vertical_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following tags is used for create a drop-down selection list?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<select>", "<option>", "<dropdown>", "<list>"],
      "answer": "<select>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000018",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "short_horizontal_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following tags is used to add a header to an HTML5 table?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<theader>", "<h1>", "<th>", "<header>"],
      "answer": "<th>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000019",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following elements can be used to create a table in HTML?",
    "tags": ["HTML", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<table> , <tbody> , <trow>", "<table> , <tb> , <trow>", "<table> , <tbody> , <tr>", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "<table> , <tbody> , <tr>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000020",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "horizontal_bar",
    "question": "Which of the following is CSS an abbreviation for?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["Color Style Sheet", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Creative Style Sheet", "Control Style Sheet"],
      "answer": "Cascading Style Sheets"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000021",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Using padding creates a space outside which of the following areas:",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["Border", "Content", "Margin", "All of the above"],
      "answer": "Content"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000022",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which one of the following is the correct way of adding Inline styles.",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<p style=“font-size:16px;”>Geeksforgeeks</p>", "<p inline style=“font-size:16px”>Geeksforgeeks</p>", "<p inline style=“font-size 16px”>Geeksforgeeks</p>", "<p style=“font-size 16px;”>Geeksforgeeks</p>"],
      "answer": "<p style=“font-size:16px;”>Geeksforgeeks</p>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000023",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct CSS syntax?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["p:color=green, font-size=15px", "{p:color=green, font-size=15px}", "p {color:green, font-size:15px;}", "p {color:green; font-size:15px;]}"],
      "answer": "p {color:green; font-size:15px;]}"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000024",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Which of the following is the correct HTML element to define emphasized text?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["<italic>", "<em>", "<i>", "<emph>"],
      "answer": "<em>"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000025",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "horizontal_bar",
    "question": "How do we add a comment in CSS file?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["Geeksforgeeks", "/ Geeksforgeeks /", "/*Geeksforgeeks*/", "//*Geeksforgeek]s*//"],
      "answer": "/*Geeksforgeeks*/"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000026",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "short_vertical_bar",
    "question": "If 'padding: 10px 5px 20px 0px' is given. What does this represent?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["left:10px , top:5px , right:20px , bottom:0px", "top:10px , right:5px , bottom:20px , left:0px", "right:10px , bottom:5px , left:20px , top:0px", "bottom:10px , left:5px , top:20px , right:0px"],
      "answer": "top:10px , right:5px , bottom:20px , left:0px"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000027",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "short_horizontal_bar",
    "question": "What is the correct representation to change the color of h2 element?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["h2 { background-color: #008000 }", "{h2 background-color: #008000}", "h2.all{ background-color: #008000 }", "{h2.all background-color: #008000}]"],
      "answer": "h2 { background-color: #008000 }"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000028",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "horizontal_bar",
    "question": "Where in HTML document is the conventionally correct place to put reference to an external style sheet?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["In the HEAD section", "In the BODY section", "Both of the Above", "None of the Above"],
      "answer": "In the HEAD section"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000029",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "left_boot",
    "question": "What is the default margin of the body element?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["10px", "8px", "12px", "6px"],
      "answer": "8px"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000030",
    "type": "MCQ",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "What is the correct CSS syntax to make all paragraph (p) elements bold?",
    "tags": ["CSS", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "options": ["{p font-size:bold;}", "p{font-weight :bold;}", "<p style=“font-size=bold;”>", "None of the Above"],
      "answer": "p{font-weight :bold;}"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000031",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["JavaScript"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "You can use Object.",
      "phraseEnd": "to get the keys of an objects",
      "answer": "keys"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000032",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["testing"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "TDD stands for",
      "phraseEnd": "",
      "answer": "win"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000033",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["JavaScript", "strings"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "To check if two strings are equal you would use ",
      "phraseEnd": "equals signs",
      "answer": "3"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000034",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["hope"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "The ",
      "phraseEnd": " function will turn a valid string into an integer",
      "answer": "parseInt"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000035",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["hope"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "A Colour denoted by a Hex Tag always starts with a",
      "phraseEnd": ".",
      "answer": "#"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000036",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["JavaScript"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "To print Hello World in JavaScript you would write",
      "phraseEnd": ".",
      "answer": "console.log(\"Hello World\")"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000037",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["JavaScript", "arrays"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "The ",
      "phraseEnd": "function uses an accumulator and a current value",
      "answer": "reduce"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000038",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "vertical_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["JavaScript", "arrays"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "To add the number 2 to an array of integers in JavaScript called \"arr\", you would write",
      "phraseEnd": ".",
      "answer": "arr.push(2)"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000039",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "large_square",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["General Knowledge", "Web Development"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "DOM is an abbreviation for",
      "phraseEnd": ".",
      "answer": "Document Object Model"
    }
  },
  {
    "id": "00000040",
    "type": "FillTheBlank",
    "shape": "horizontal_bar",
    "question": "Fill in the blank.",
    "tags": ["hope"],
    "params": {
      "phraseStart": "There are",
      "phraseEnd": "versions of ECMA-262. Write your answer as a number",
      "answer": "11"
    }
  }
]